Your arms go through the sleeves like this.
Then you cross the left side over the right.
And that's all you have to do.
Easy, huh?
Like this.
Oh, man, look at all that potential.
I just hope she keeps growing into her body.
Come on, what do you call these clothes again?
There's people with a fetish for that sort of thing.
I think I see where they're coming from.
It's a type of kimono called a yukata.
Oh, and there's a festival going on today at the shrine nearby.
Oh, master.
Well, fun while it lasted.
Get out of here, you smart bird!
Thank you.
I can't hear my heart, but I can't stop the door
I can't hear my heart, but I can't hear my mind
Can't you hear my heart, babe?
Can't you hear the words?
ckets
that the Age of Exploration, which started in the 15th century,
was an era of brutal colonization
when the people of Western Europe
began exploring and mapping the globe.
It's said in the right hand, the Europeans carried a gun
and in the left, a Bible.
Everywhere they traveled, they discovered new worlds
and wasted little time in occupying them.
In many ways, the invention of the musket
was the ultimate symbol of mankind's subjugation
over these newly conquered worlds.
In the right hand, a gun.
Wow, look at all the people here this year.
There's cotton candy.
Oh, and takoyaki and yakisoba!
Why do you ever yap about his food?
So, what's it to you?
If you keep eating like this, you'll get fat.
You're just kidding! Forget I said anything!
Hey, Nim, you want one?
No way!
Yo, Icarus, let me know if you want anything.
I'll buy it for you.
Oh, Icarus, let me know if you want anything.
All right, please.
What?
I think one will suffice!
Tomo!
Come check out these other booths with me!
Be right there!
What's all this?
Holy crap!
Welcome to my booth.
Can we go, Tomoki?
Can we go, Tomiki?
Gun freaks like this kind of weird me out.
There are only guns and ammunition.
I don't see any prizes.
If this is a rifle range,
where are the targets we're supposed to shoot at?
Sugata, what are you doing here?
Oh, Mikuko invited me along.
What is a festival exactly?
I believe a festival is an event
that the entire town can enjoy together as one.
Mikuko?
That's why we, the Satsukatane family,
have hired a pro to oversee a night of fun
and danger in the woods.
Our hope is that it will unite the entire town.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
The rules are simple.
We will play a game of survival using these court guns.
The last person standing will win a truly fantastic prize.
A fantastic prize, huh?
Ten million yen in cold, hard cash.
Interesting.
That would be quite the windfall.
Enough to buy your dreams.
Sugata?
Wow, that sounds like a blast.
What do you say, Tomo?
You want to do it?
Hmm.
I can't deny it.
Ten million sounds pretty damn nice.
But I can't shake the feeling
like something's going to go horribly wrong.
Hey, Nymph, are you getting cold feet?
Just not interested.
Not in the slightest.
Okay, fellow neighbors.
Are you ready?
Then let's get crazy
and shoot the living hell out of each other.
May the survival game begin.
No way I'm letting myself get caught in the crossfire.
Just need to find a nice, secure place to hide.
Where do you think you're going, skinny boy?
It's the old bag from the community center.
I thought you had a bad hip.
It was a miracle.
The pain just vanished
as soon as I heard about the 10 mil.
Get your ass back here!
Show me number six!
Don't you know I should have changed your diapers?
Stay right there.
You're mine, bitch!
The veggie lady?
Move one inch and you're dead.
The fishmonger?
Look, girls.
There goes Tomoki.
The girls from my class, too?
Why the hell is everyone after me?
Oh, come now, Tomoki.
It's nice to feel love.
This is love.
I want no part of it.
Let's go.
Hope I'm safe now.
The hell you are!
Oh, crap!
I'm taking you out!
Whoa, Grandma.
I know!
We got a sniper!
Where's he at?
He's in the trees!
There must be another sniper nearby.
That round was shot with a cunning level of stealth.
It was accurate, missing me by mere inches.
There's no doubt who it is.
Mikako.
I knew it!
You are quite skilled.
You are not so bad yourself.
Holy crap!
Someone freaking sent me!
Looks like we're at a stalemate.
Well, then let's fight dirty.
And if I knew this was gonna happen, I would have let you guys shoot me before the game even started!
Here we go!
What?
What is that?
This is the end of the world.
God has come to destroy us.
This is his final judgment.
Hey!
Don't you think you're overdoing it a bit?
You've had your fun, now get down here and stay out of trouble.
Yes, Master.
Man, since I got a lot of people, really thinned out the competition.
Of course, now I have an actual chance at bagging the ten million.
Yes, time to murder!
What did it feel like, brutally slaughtering all those pathetic little people below you?
Bring back any memories?
Of course it doesn't.
We both know all your memory and thought processes are protected.
I'd be more than happy to help you remember who you really are.
Uranus Queen, the frightening entity who shook the synapse to its very core?
Well now, did that happen to jog any memories in that stubborn head of yours?
I am a pet class, Angeloid, type Alpha.
A pet class? Don't make me laugh.
I have been given strict orders by my own master to return you back to the synapse.
That which is lost must be returned to its rightful owner, Alpha.
This is why I warned you to be careful.
I am Nymph, an electronic warfare class Angeloid, type Beta, and I have come here to take you home, Uranus Queen.
I am a pet class Angeloid.
Stop saying that! Wake up!
Oops, looks like I may have gone a little overboard.
I am... a pet class Angeloid.
Fine, then I guess you leave me no choice. I'll remove your memory protection with my hacking system.
And once I'm finished, you'll understand why I scoff at the idea of you being a pet class anything!
I... what is this I'm seeing?
Icarus, I command you to destroy those surface insects. Take no prisoners.
Yes, master.
These memories... what are they?
Make it stop!
I'm sorry I got mad at you last night. I swear, it's just... you look like some killer android weapon. Like you'd see in a movie or something.
I guess it caught me off guard and I kind of freaked out.
Master...
Hmph.
Was it really so bad you had to burst into tears?
Guess your dream of being a pet class has exploded in your face!
Wait... it doesn't make sense. How are you... able to cry?
I didn't finish. I removed your memory protections but never actually disabled your thought protections.
Emotional protection...
Emotional protection removal 100%.
Variable wing protection removal processing.
No! Is she...
90.
Self-repair sequence activated.
Functionality protection removal processing.
I think the Uranus Queen is about to reawaken.
Self-recovery complete.
Target... lock on.
Commence firing Artemis.
What happened? Why are all the protections removed? Now she's fully awakened!
Son of a...
It's mud! I've got mud on my face! How gross!
It's so nasty! I'm disgusting! I ate mud!
I'm gonna... rip you into shreds!
Paradex...
Sol!
A... Aegis!
Cat!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Hold it! You're gonna destroy the whole country with that!
No, just you. When the projectile hits its point of contact, I'll set Aegis to full power, protecting everything else.
That's ridiculous! You'd end up hurting yourself as much as me!
I will be returning to my master. I am a pet-class angeloid. Type Alpha Icarus.
Please, Nymph. Go home. Leave.
I beg you.
Okay, fine. But...
How much longer do you think you'll be able to fool him, huh?
I can't help but wonder what your true master would think if you learned what you were doing here.
Little Miss Weapon of DEATH!
Master told me to stay out of trouble. But I did not. I failed him.
Oh, man. How many left can there be? This game's like a damn zombie movie. It's really wearing my ass out.
Hey, are you even listening to me?
What the hell? Don't tell me you're using a real freaking gun!
Well, sort of. I mixed in a live round.
I did that to a few of the guns, so don't be surprised if it happens again.
Tomo, I found you!
Huh?
I've been looking for you. I searched everywhere, but you were gone. It sucks being left behind.
Bastard!
Hey, gun dude! Does that one have real bullets too?
Head to the sky, Tomoki!
Wow! They sure don't make toys like they used to! That felt like the real thing!
Swaro wings! You're insane!
This is so much fun!
Dr. Perser, don't you realize you're shooting real bullets?
I'm so close to winning this thing, I can taste it!
I'll do whatever it takes to get my hands on that ten million!
I can think of so many things I can do with that much cash!
The possibilities are endless!
Like I can take Tomo to an amusement park!
Or we can go on a trip together!
Then once we're back in the room for the night...
Oh, Tomo, what's that? You want to get in the bath with me?
You silly Pervo!
Tomo's a creep! Tomo's a creep! Tomo's a Pervo creep!
Tomo's a Pervo creep! Don't wreck your little ass out!
I'm getting already!
No, wait! Stay back!
Listen to me!
Do you realize we're the only people left in the game?
I have a one-in-two chance of winning!
Okay, I get it. You really want to win.
But even if you did, what would you even do with ten million?
I would. I'd make you.
No!
I can't say it! It's too embarrassing, you filthy disgusting Pervo!
I can't say it!
Somebody save me!
What... just happened?
HIKORUS!
Yes?
Man, what the heck is your skin made of, anyway?
I thought we'd lost you there.
Hm. So anyone see where Nymph ran off to?
She probably got bored and went home. You know how she is.
I wouldn't really worry about it too much.
Let's address the elephant in the room. Who's gonna win the ten million?
Oh, right. It's still on.
It looks like the only two left are you and Suhara.
Should make for an interesting finish.
Son of a bitch!
Not quite. You forgot someone.
Let's have some fun, Mama's boy.
Boom.
Good boy.
No, no, no, no.
And the winner is the guy from the Rifle Range.
Your half, as promised, sir.
Thank you.
See you next year!
What? You want to do this again?
We'll be right back.
Look at this. What happened? Your Yucata's all dirty.
What the hell? Are you all right? Your arm's covered in bruises.
I'm fine.
It's so weird.
Your skin feels as soft as a real girl's, and yet somehow a bullet bounced off it.
Like it was made of rubber.
So did you jump in front of that bullet for me because you knew you wouldn't get hurt?
No. I was as surprised as you.
Oh, great. You were surprised.
You had no idea what would happen to you.
Look, it was nice and old, but don't ever do it again.
I know you think you have to risk your own life to protect mine.
That whole concept makes me uneasy.
You're a person, too.
You shouldn't have to be put in that kind of situation.
The delusional story that began with a lie.